By the way...That is one gorgeous bed.
顺便说一下... 那是一个极好的床
Yeah, it's okay.
是  它还行吧
Maybe we could share?
也许我们能分享
You know, one night you get the bed. The next night, I do.
你知道  一个晚上你得到  (睡)  床  (的机会) 下一个晚上  我睡床
-That kind of thing.-You know, this bed is mine.
-那一类的事 -你知道  这床是我的
You? You get an old blanket.That suits you.
你  你有个旧毯子 那个很配你
You're an old-blanket kind of a dog.
你是  (配)  旧毯子的那种狗
You are stubborn.
你很难对付
Hey, I get it. I'm stubborn, too.
嘿  我懂了  我也很难对付
But we gotta learn to get along.
但是我们得学着和睦相处
-Wait. What are you...-I bet we can both fit in this bed if we really try.
-等等  你在...-我打赌我们能都适合在这张床上如果我们真的试试
-Let me scoot on in there.-No, wait.
-让我溜  (一圈)  在上面那儿-不 等等
Perfect. This is comfy, right?
完美  这很舒服  是吧
No, it is not.
一不  这不  (舒服)
I'm comfy.
我很舒服